

# **Jonathan Pierce**

Senior UI/UX Designer

https://jonathanpiercedesign.com

What started as a love for visual design and applications, evolved into a blend of solving complex UX problems and delivering clean, effective, front-end experiences. My experience with multi-platform organizations has taught me the value in thinking large by applying Atomic Design principles to modern design systems.

#### CONTACT

Ozark, MO 434-907-8324 piercedesign22@gmail.com

#### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Science 2006 - 2010 Communication Studies Liberty University, Lynchburg, VA

#### **APPS & SKILLS**

Sketch InVision

Adobe Creative Cloud

**Adobe Experience Manager** 

**Responsive Design** 

**Application Design** 

iOS Design

**Design Systems** 

**Atomic Design** 

Agile

**Google Analytics** 

JIRA/Confluence

Github

HTML5/Sass

**Zurb Foundation** 

**Bootstrap** 

**Branding** 

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Bass Pro Shops 2015 - Current

## Senior UI/UX Designer in Springfield, MO

Responsible for the UI/UX design for White River Marine Group; the parent company for marine brands like Tracker, Ranger, Nitro, Mako, Triton, Bass Pro Boating Center and more. This role's primary focus is centered around the migration to Adobe Experience Manager (AEM) for all brand websites. Aside from the UI/UX design, this includes creating and maintaining a central design system and component library, UX design for AEM internal authors and story writing for product requirements

# Dapper Shopping, Inc. 2014 - 2015

# Lead UI/UX Designer in San Francisco, CA

Responsible for the overall UI/UX of the iOS app Dapper (for men) and Moxy (for women). Other roles include brand identity design, wireframing concepts, prototyping interactions, quality assurance and testing, design and HTML/CSS of the marketing website, design and HTML for transaction emails and marketing materials for web/print media.

#### Liberty University 2012 - 2014

## Senior UI Designer in Lynchburg, VA

Design team lead for all web and app related projects. Responsible for creating and enforcing brand guidelines, prioritizing and assigning projects to designers and wireframing overall UX of each product. Projects included iOS and Android applications, responsive websites, complex internal web applications and student facing app tools.

## **TRAINING & AWARDS**

# **Apple App Store Feature**

Moxy, April 2015 Best New Apps and Lifestyle

Dapper, November 2014
Best New Apps, Lifestyle and Buy
with Apple Pay

# Reach Design Leadership Conference

2017 New York, NY

# **Adobe Summit**

2018 Las Vegas, NV

# Nielsen Norman Group

UX Training 2017 Chicago, IL UX Training 2012 Chicago, IL

#### 2012 AMA Prism Award

Corporate Identity
Pickering Creative Group

# Pickering Creative Group 2010 - 2012

# Graphic Designer in Lynchburg, VA

Designed and developed ideas for various clients along the midwest and east coast. Included branding, web design, web development, print advertising, and marketing strategies.